

Valentina Molina | Volleyball player

Professional Profile

I am Valentina Molina Perez, I have been playing volleyball for 6 years of my 17 years of live. The positions which I stand out in are libero and defensive specialist and, positions where I got recognitions, furthermore I played as an Outside Hitter for 14-s division in national state tournaments.

Sports have been my passion for more than 14 years. The early beginning improved my dedication, perseverance, and leadership skills. I have been also part of Colombian National learn in gymnastics, hip hop dance and cheerleader, sports that join all the necessary abilities that your college is looking for!

Core Skills

- · Leadership
- Velocity
- Communication
- Organization

- Flexibility
- Team support
- Perseverance
- Intelligence

Career Summary

Defensive Specialist, Kansas Raise Volleyball Club 18s-1

Dec 2021- Present

Defensive Specialist #32. Recorded Highlight in Oklahoma, Nebraska and Kansas, in which the defense, dives, serves and serve receives are the statistically highlighted. Las Vegas and Lawrence are the next goals to achieve and with the hard practice and big mentality we are going to be ready for that!

Defensive Specialist, Huila
Feb 2021- Jun 2022
Colombian State National Team

Defensive Specialist #3. After a year of practice for the most important tournament Sub-21, where Colombian National team recruits, Valentina Molina was a highlighted defensive specialist of the tournament, getting high statistics in her serve receives skills.

Education

Colombo Ingles del Huila• Class of 2022 | Overall GPA: 4.5/5.0 | bed 2021- Oct 2023 | Year of graduation-Honorable Academics Recognitions:

4 Elementary School- English Recognitions for Outstanding grades.

5th Grade honorable certificate "For having obtained an Excellent Academic Performance during the year 2016"

6th Grade honorable certificate "For its superior performance in the area of Spanish Language"

First place in a Poem Recitation-State 2017

Science gold trophy-First place in "First Bilingual Olympiads in Science Nicola Tesla"

11th Grade recognition of top 3 students in the country by 'Universidad National de Colombia' (Colombo Ingles del Huila convent with Universidad Nacional de Colombia- called "Mejor bachillerato")

11th grade- Recognition by 'Entrenando' for being one of the best scores in Colombia "Simulacro Icfes" 480/500"

Cambridge Certification: "Council Europe Level B1"

Life Prep Academy- Class of 2023 / currently GPA 3.87 / Aug 2022 – Apr 2023 / Perform for volleyball and soccer team/ Participated in government debates.

Additional

Hobbies & Interests

Public Speaking

Languages

English, Spanish